

# NIKOLA MILENKOVSKI CURRICULUM VITAE

#### **LOCATION**

Skopje, North Macedonia

#### **EMAIL**

milenkovskin@gmail.com

#### **MOBILE**

(+389) 70912190

#### **LINKEDIN**

https://www.linkedin.com/in/milenkovskin

#### **SKILLS**

UX/UI Designer
HTML & CSS
C/C++
PHP
Swift (Beginner)

Responsibility
Flexibility
Communication
Coordination
Teamwork

#### **LANGUAGES**

Macedonian (Native)
English (Advanced)
Serbian (Advanced)
Italian (Beginner)

#### **PROFILE**

An FCSE graduate student in Skopje, North Macedonia. My past experience include working with UX/UI design, front-end and back-end technologies. I consider myself to be very organized, timely and professional when it comes to my work and school life. I am very efficient in problem solving and producing the optimal results within my set deadlines. I constantly gain valuable knowledge through formal and informal education.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Web Development Intern | Wordfella, Skopje February - March; September - November 2020

In this company I was working as a web developer internt and I was included in two projects. For the first one I was working with front-end (HTML, CSS, SCSS with BEM methodology, WordPress) and back-end technologies (PHP). As for the second, I was working as UX/UI Designer and front-end developer.

#### Web Developer Intern | SRD Technology, Skopje November 2017 - April 2018

As a web developer intern in a product-based company, I was integrating company applications which supported SAML 2.0, with our product. I was part of the Admin Portal to organize, manage and display the data about companies and users of a product. In the whole process I was working with TypeScript, HTML, CSS. (product – Saaspass)

#### Intern | GdiDATA, Skopje May 2017 - June 2017

Purpose of the internship was finishing a project for a university subject. We had a training for one week to work with ArcGIS Software in the licensed company GisDATA in Skopje. Creating a digital version of a map of a local town Berovo in the interest of simplifying it and making the user experience friendlier, by mapping the features of the town, its buildings and attributing the features.

## **PROJECTS**

# Digitized Map – ArcGIS (2017)

Digitalization from the analog maps to informative, interactional digital map of a local town Berovo, with all distinct places and buildings.

## **EDUCATION**

UX/UI Academy September 2020 - ongoing

Academy for UX/UI, Brainster – Skopje Certificate for UX/UI Designer

**University September 2014 - ongoing** 

Ss. Cyril and Methodius University – Skopje Bachelor of Science, Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering